

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **FPT UNIVERSITY DA NANG**

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

2018 - 2023

Graduation classified pretty good

## Hồ Văn Phức

### Java Developer

#### **PROFILE**

phuchv1708@gmail.com

0374643135

tttps://www.facebook.com/vanphuc1708

TT Hue - VietNam

With trained expertise and more than 6 months working at the company, as well as some programming knowledge and skills that I have accumulated during my student period, along with good self-study ability, I am ready learn new knowledge to match the position I am applying for as well as the position I will work for. I applied for the position of JAVA Programmer (Frsher) with the desire to develop myself, improve transferable skills and have the opportunity to participate in the company's project.

#### **SKILLS**

#### **BACK-END**

 Java core, OOP, MVC model, RESTful API with Spring boot, Three layer architecture, ...

#### **DATABASE**

- Experience working with Firebase in graduation project
- Basic knowledge NoSQL and SQL: Redis, SQL server, MySQL
- Experience working with Mongodb, Elasticsearch, Kafka on company project

#### **OTHER**

- Experience use code tool: IntelliJ, eclipse, Git, ... at work
- Read and understand English documents
- Learn and practice about Red5pro livestream technology
- Learn knowledge about design pattern mongoDB
- Basic knowledge: HTML, CSS, Javascript

#### **ACTIVITIES**

05/2021 - 08/2021

# On-the-job training FSOFT Da Nang Fond-End Developer

• Join to learn basic website programming knowledge: HTML, CSS, SQL Server, .Net, ...

10/2022 - 06/2023

### Hahalolo Travel Social Network Back-End Developer

 Java Developer at HAHALOLO TRAVEL SOCIAL NETWORK JOINT STOCK COMPANY

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

05/2021 - 08/2021

ON-THE-JOB TRAINING FSOFT DA NANG (GROUP)

#### **FOND-END DEVELOPER**

**Product Description:** This is a system that allows users to post and auction products, in addition to support website management through functions such as statistics, accepting auction products, ...

**My responsibilities:** Analysis and design UI/UX, Development, Testing **Technologies used:** 

.Net, Sql Server, Paypal service, ...

#### 05/2022 - 08/2022

# GRADUATION PROJECT AT SCHOOL (GROUP)

#### **BACK-END DEVERLOP**

**Product Description:** This is a website and mobile application system to support cafe management, in which the mobile platform helps users to place orders, manage orders, evaluate products..., the website platform helps employees manage orders, administrators can manage products, manage employees, users, manage discount codes, statistics.

**My responsibilities:** Analysis and design UI/UX, Design Database, Develop website and deploy, Code review, Testing

#### **Technologies used:**

- · Website: Use Java spring boot and React
- Mobile App: KotlinDatabase: FireBase
- Other: Use Three service Momopay, Zalopay and Google map API

Link project: https://gitlab.com/haukutekontum/coffee\_shop

#### 10/2022 - 06/2023

# HAHALOLO TRAVEL SOCIAL NETWORK JOINT STOCK COMPANY

#### **BACK-END DEVERLOP**

**Description:** Learning, building and developing features for company website. **My responsibilities:** 

- · Complete MongoDB Certifications
- Learn and practice RESTFul API using Spring boot + MongoDB
- Building and developing features related to Tours in the company, including: writing new functions, updating and improving the performance of old functions.
- Sync batch data and re-sync data for some collections in the tour
- Participate in mapping design(Elasticsearch) for some data storage models

#### Technologies used:

- MongoDB
- Java Spring Boot
- Kafka
- Elasticsearch

**HONORS & AWARDS** 

Link Web: https://www.hahalolo.com/

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

08/2021

#### \_\_\_\_

### Certificate ACADEMIC PREPARATORY

ENGLISH

Ist prize in the auction website system product during the internship period at FPT, majoring in .Net languages

I like EMD, play game and interact with friends ....

**INTERESTS** 

#### 2021

2020

Certificate the program "On the job training"at the FPT Software Central Company Limited

© topcv.vn